<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dean Sallinen</title>
    <link>http://deansallinen.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dean Sallinen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2017 Dean Sallinen</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:44:32 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://deansallinen.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BCVotes.info</title>
      <link>http://deansallinen.ca/portfolio/bc-votes-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:44:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deansallinen.ca/portfolio/bc-votes-info/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A website to help citizens find their local candidates and compare party platforms in the
BC Provincial Election.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last Skytrain</title>
      <link>http://deansallinen.ca/portfolio/the-last-skytrain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deansallinen.ca/portfolio/the-last-skytrain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A mobile website to simplify the late night train finding experience by rethinking data visualization.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferry Tracker</title>
      <link>http://deansallinen.ca/portfolio/ferry-tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deansallinen.ca/portfolio/ferry-tracker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An Android app to view the BC Ferries schedule, follow sailings, and be notified about schedule changes.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS Grid Layout Practice</title>
      <link>http://deansallinen.ca/experiments/gridlayout-figma-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 19:04:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deansallinen.ca/experiments/gridlayout-figma-logo/</guid>
      <description>The following is an exercise I did while teaching myself CSS Grid Layout with the help of Rachel Andrew&amp;rsquo;s Grid By Example.
I thought the new Figma logo could be easily created using only HTML and CSS with Grid Layout.
I worked on improving my eye for RGB colour blending by not using an eyedropper tool to get exact values.
See the Pen Grid Layout Figma Logo  by Dean (@deza604) on CodePen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get in touch!</title>
      <link>http://deansallinen.ca/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 13:00:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deansallinen.ca/contact/</guid>
      <description>Whether it&amp;rsquo;s feedback on one of my projects or an idea you want to collaborate on, I would love to hear from you!
I usually respond to email within a day, and I check social media around once a week. Gotta stay productive!
Are you hiring? I&amp;rsquo;m currently looking for internships or Junior UX/UI roles to improve my skills and tackle new challenges.
Send me an email if you might be interested, and we can arrange a time to chat!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://deansallinen.ca/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deansallinen.ca/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a designer from Vancouver BC currently focused on User Experience and User Interface.
I come from an academic background in Psychology. Studying human behaviour has given me invaluable insights, along with research and interviewing skills which I use in my design process.
My work history spans industries and job titles and I see my varied experience as a benefit when designing for end users.
When I&amp;rsquo;m not working on my design projects I enjoy learning new songs on guitar, discovering new Celiac friendly foods, and playing with my adopted rabbit Max.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>